Thank you for watching!
Good evening, everyone. The morning chimes have rung and it's us,
CJB mainstay.
Before we start the show, I would like to quickly choose today's MC.
Please vote for your favorite number from 1 to 3.
The person holding the number card with that number on it will be today's MC.
Let's start voting!
Among 1, 2, and 3.
See you again, here in front.
It's the first time since last year.
Yutaka and the others have already drawn their numbers and are holding them.
We have it.
The first place winner will be the MC. That's right.
I wonder who it will be. It's been a long time since last year, right? It's been a long time. First time since last year, right?
Japanese number? I won't tell you.
I wonder who it is. You won't show me, will you? No, I won't.
Okay, 54321, can-can-can. Who's in first place?
That was fast.
Oh, 45.5% of 3, number 3. So we have the number 3.
Yuma!
So cute!
Yes, I'm number 2.
I'm number 1.
Why?
Good luck, Yuma!
I'm a little worried.
Can you read? Can you read?
Anyway, Yuma, please be today's MC.
I'm Yuno Kokubo and I'll be your MC today. My name is Yuno Kokubo.
I will do my best.
Do your best!
I'm scared.
Okay, I'll go now.
Let's begin.
The hilarious and huffing and puffing showroom in the middle of the shrimp!
Yay!
Yes, thank you very much for watching the 46th EBichu's Delightful and Fufufula Showroom today.
Thank you very much.
The EBICHU's Delightful and Fufufula Showroom is the sister show of our sister showroom, Uka-san's showroom.
Yes, I know.
Then we will announce the ranking and...oh, I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
Sorry, sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Are you still doing it?
No, not yet.
Now you're the MC.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Anyway, I will announce the ranking from No. 5 to No. 1.
Yes!
Fifth place in the ranking.
Fifth place goes to.
Sixth place.
Sixth Family?
Yes, sir. Thank you very much.
4th place, Mr. Shumai.
Thank you very much.
2nd place, Tamamii-san.
1st place, Mr. Motta.
Thank you very much.
Yes, we have a new avatar for you. You can get the original avatar of Ebichu Showroom by registering to our showroom,
You can get it by gifting it to us for free or for a fee.
Yes.
There are many avatars.
It's true.
Yes, there are a lot of avatars. There are a lot of avatars.
There are so many.
Thank you very much.
Please become an avatar of Ebichu.
Yes.
If you click on the Twitter symbol at the bottom of the screen, you can spread the word about this distribution on Twitter.
Thank you very much.
Okay. So, it's time to spread the word.
Yes.
In order for as many people as possible to see this broadcast, we will be tweeting an announcement on Twitter, so please retweet it.
Please retweet.
What pose do you want to do?
Yes, I'll do it.
You can decide on a new one.
I'll go with this one.
This one?
The ears? The ones in the ears?
The ones in your ears?
It looks like an earphone riot.
Not quite.
A little different.
Okay, let's go with Riot.
Riot.
Riot after all these years.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Thank you.
Okay, bye. Bye.Yes, sir. Bye.
Retweet.
Yes. Please do.
Yes. As a group.
As a group, yes.
On the 28th of May, there will be a performance of EbiJoo Drawer in Aichi.
Yes, we did.
It was my triumphant return live performance.
How was it?
I was nervous.
I was so nervous.
I was really stiff.
It was the same with Coconan. In Ibaraki, Coconan was really nervous.
I was really nervous in Ibaraki. He was really nervous.
I was really nervous when I came back to Japan.
He was someone I might have passed by at the same station.
I'm sure.
I'm in my hometown now.
That's for sure.
That's right.
But my parents and friends were there.
I was nervous.
All my relatives.
I got a lot of gifts.
Sweet potato onimanju.
Yes, onimanju was very delicious.
They were delicious.
Thank you very much.
I think Grandpa is watching us right now.
Thank you, Grandpa.
How was Aichi Park, everyone?
How was it?
Did anyone go?
I wonder if everyone ate something from Aichi or something like that.
I wonder if they ate.
Oni manju and some kind of sweet potato manju.
Yes.
It's about the same size as a sweet potato, but it's delicious.
It was really delicious.
Onimanju is something that people from Aichi Prefecture would understand, but I thought they buy it.
It's something you make at home.
You make them.
That's right.
I was so surprised.
The venue was beautiful.
Indeed.
Thank you very much.
I had hitsu-mabushi.
Hitsujimabushi was really delicious.
Yes, we had hitsujimabushi for dinner after the event.
It was really delicious.
I'm glad.
Did you go home?
I went home and ate grilled bean sprouts.
Isn't that like Aichi?
I also ate tomatoes.
She said she had onimanju.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Yuno introduced me to this place, right?
A restaurant.
Jikamachi in Inuyama.
I want to go there too.
I think there is a video of Ebichu on YouTube right now.
I'd like to see it.
And June 3rd is the Ebichu Drawer performance in Hachioji.
Yes, Hachioji.
Hachioji.
Repeat.
It was originally the first day.
Thank you very much for those who waited for it.
I thought you were waiting for me.
Yes.
We played all the songs from the album in Hachioji,
How was it? How was it?
Did you come?
I played a song that I pushed too.
It's "Curun", isn't it?
A lovely aroma.
I'm going to spoil it now.
I know. Sorry.
I did a tekimeki tekimeki tekimeki suteron with Kurun.
It was our first performance.
Isn't Fritz from Kurun so cute?
So cute.
The formation was amazing.
It was so cool.
It was cool and cute.
At first, they danced in two halves.
The formation is fun, isn't it?
I never get tired of watching it.
It's amazing how sleepless Everyman sang like he was so happy.
She even spun around on her stomach.
Yes, they did.
It was fun.
It was a lot of fun.
And so was Tekimeki.
That choreography is interesting.
It's interesting.
It's the same person who put in the choreography for the dress-up bar.The same person who put in the pretending bar.
She was followed by Ms. Natsumi Takenaka.
It's very interesting.
It's really difficult, but it's fun.
It's really fun.
It's fun.
Dancing.
The choreography is interesting, but it's also cool.
Yes, it's true.
You should come to the show and see the choreography.
There are many people who haven't seen it yet.
I hope you look forward to it.
We don't know when we are going to do it.
We don't know what songs we will play.
Please come to all the shows.
I hope you come to all the shows.
You had Hamafest on May 29, didn't you?
That's right.
At the stadium.
It was hot.
Hot.
Isn't it the first time? Now.
Now, maybe in the summer.
First time outdoors.
Yes.
This year, I mean, already.
Yeah.
It's the first time we did it in the heat.
It's the first time.
That's right.
It was like a side project of the Fami Ensemble.
The number of songs is different.
It was really like a preparation for that.
But it was great.
It was hot and I was wearing black clothes during rehearsals.
I was wearing a neck T-shirt, black shorts, and black pants.
It was the middle of the day and the sun was beating down on me.
Everything was black, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
It was amazing.
You said, "Kokonar, that's enough," and took off your jacket.
That's all.
It was for sun protection. He took off his jacket.
He even opened his arms.
Like a no stream.
Everyone said it was too hot.
I wonder if they were okay with the sunburn.
I was fine.
But you got sunburned.
It should be fine.
I'll be back.
I put on a lot of sunscreen.
Yes, you did. You'll get sunburned.
You'll get sunburnt, but it was fun.
It was fun.
It was amazing.
There were so many people.
It was such a big venue, and so many people came.
It was hot.
It was hot after all.
But I was thinking of going with the team from "Cannai Debut".
What do you mean it wasn't a project for Cannai Debut?
A game?
Yes. We played some games.
It was fun.
It was a lot of fun.
Also, Team Kuchi danced for us with tissues.
They gave us power.
Thank you very much.
After that, I didn't get to see much of us,
But I could hear their voices.
I wanted to see it.
Is there a girl who tans easily? I heard.
Who tans easily?
No.
Yeah.
What's with you all of a sudden?
People who get sunburnt.
People who get dark.
People who get darker.
I get darker, too.
Who gets darker?
I'm the one who turns red.
I'm a person who turns red.
It comes back soon.
I'm the type of person who turns red quickly.
You don't turn black?
No, I don't.
It's all black.
When I wear a mask, it's the most embarrassing thing to get burned by it.
It's embarrassing to have marks on your face when you take it off, so you have to be very careful with your face.
I have to be very careful with my face. I applied it on my body as well, but I also applied it on my face several times.
I applied it to my body, but I had to reapply it many times to my face.
I also sprayed it on my head.Spray on the head and stuff.
It was on my head, too.
I see.
When I had my hair cut, I was told that my scalp was burned.
What?
Really?
I won't show you.
It's burned.
I heard it burns.
My scalp burns too.
The day we shot the music video for "Youth Zombies" was hot, right?
It was hot.
We shot a lot outside, so my friends told me I got burnt that day.
I see. You got burnt again that day at the Powerful festival?
Please be careful.
Please take precautions against sunburn.
I'll be back soon.
It was a lot of fun, wasn't it? Hello! Hello!
It's been a while since I've seen you in your college arts and crafts costume.
That's for sure.
Wearing costumes in the members' colors.
It's cute, isn't it? That costume.
That outfit is cute.
Really.
But some of you may have never seen that outfit before,
I think it's easy to recognize because of the member's color.
We didn't have many member colors.
Since you joined us.
That's right.
But I think it is a little bit.
I was talking about something completely unrelated the other day.
It's no longer relevant.
It is.
It's fine.
I was doing an assignment on TV.
I was doing an assignment, and I turned on the TV, and there was a big arts and crafts show on,
I was watching it, and I thought that Nonaka's pure white made her look like an amazing fairy.
I thought, "That's right.
I was amazed.
I've always been transparent, so when I wear white, I look transparent.
You can't see it.
It's like an aura.
It was like they came to see me in white.
My family came to see it, too,
They said the back was amazing.
But it's really cute.
The colors are really cute.
They really look good together.
Aya, you're a fairy, too.
That's for sure.
The way her hair looks.
The yellow-green and green outfits go really well together.
I feel like a forest fairy.
That's for sure.
She was cool.
She's really cute.
This is the one that our auto-recorder reacted to.
The color is almost like lighting.
It's true.
It's been glowing since the 7th.
I see...the two from the college arts and crafts show.
The two fairies?
Ah, yes.
Unit.
The college arts and crafts, that's right, that's right.
Fairies.
Two fairies.
And they're wearing white outfits in Ebbetweeners, too.
That's what the Ebbetweeners are, too.
The story is exactly the same.
Let's go back, let's go back.
Please follow me.
Yes.
Even the drawer has fluffy tulle in the member's color.
Not white.
Member color.
The bottom is yellow or pink, but the top is member-colored.
That's cute too, isn't it?
That's cute.
They're cute.
They're following me.
They're following us.
That's good, that's good.
Is she with us?
Thank you very much.
The current drawer outfits are all green.
Talking about drawers.
What are you talking about?
They all have costumes that look like some princess's.
The one in the member's color.
You're wearing the first one.
I think they are cute.
The ones with me and stuff.
Do you have a favorite costume?
When we have nine members.
I guess the college students' group.
I like that blue costume.
For the college students' group.
It's so cool.It's so cool.
It's nice, isn't it?
I'm hot.
I got wet.
It depends on the person.
I'm wearing those.
Shorts?
Yes, shorts.
And they have boots in them, so they're cool.
What do they like? I don't know.
I like the blue ones.
Familiars.
A skull.
Skulls are cute.
It's a little hot.
I wonder how this year's Familiarization is going to be?
I'm sure.
I'm curious.
Ear line.
Earphones.
Liota.
Raiota.
The first one.
That one is cute.
Navel button.
Yes, it is.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's the one that didn't make the cut.
You failed in the navel cut.
You were in the sleeveless selection.
Sleeveless selection.
Since then, I've been wearing sleeveless clothes a lot.
That's right.
I really like that outfit.
Mondrian costume.
Asha's current outfit.
Mondrian Asha's.
I'm sure.
I haven't worn it much.
I want to wear it at the concert.
The collar is cute.
Oh, I see.
They're alternately different.
That's true.
It's cute.
Sleeveless selection.
That's me, Yuna. That's...
The center is good, too.
Fluffy.
It's cute.
It's cute, isn't it?
I heard it's belly button season.
Oh, it's true.
I'm going to cut it all off.
I'm afraid I'm going to cut it all off.
They're all going to be cut off.
All the fans, all the people who are in favor of Coconut, are going to show their navels.
That's interesting, isn't it?
They are all pushing for it.
The hats in the center were cute.
Costumes with hats.
Gray bow.
The hair ornament is cute, isn't it?
It's cute.
Everything is cute.
But this year's Famien, you know?
The first one, you know, I think everyone knows the outfit.
White.
Is it nice?
It's okay.
I don't know, a white costume and a plain clothes style costume.
I don't know.
I don't know...
I wonder what would happen if I told you earlier.
I don't know yet.
I wonder if it will be cool.
It's time for Coco to win at Savondis.
You could have won if you had stuck out your navel.
If you said you couldn't win.
Can she win? If you show your navel.
You might win.
That's right.
That's for sure.
I have high expectations.
So, for those of you who are pushing for Coconut, I'd like to ask you all to put out your navels.
Support.
Get out your belly button.
Support Coconar.
Please.
Please, please, please.
It's time to move on.
First of all, here's a project.
Seishun Zombies Music Video Watching Party.
This is a section for everyone to watch the music video of Seishun Zombies, which was released on the 10th anniversary of their major label debut.
Is there anything you would like to tell us about Seishun Zombies first?
You are going to tell it as it is.
Is there anything you would like to tell us about the Seishun Zombies first?If you would like to talk about Youth Zombies first.
I wonder if any of you have seen it.
I wonder if anyone has.
I wonder if everyone has seen it.
You have seen it, right?
On the other hand, I'd like to talk about those who haven't seen it yet.
Let's watch it together.
But I'm going to talk about it here.
I see.
I'll tell them I saw it in the premium release.
Oh, here they are.
Shaved ice gals.
That's right.
They were really messing around.
We had fun filming and playing.
It all happened so fast.
We just played around.
We were all playing together.
There were various scenes.
There were karaoke scenes and so on.
There were a lot of scenes.
We also paid attention to the costumes.
I wore a lot of different outfits, so costumes.
Yes.
They are so cute.
Shall we start?
Yes.
Okay, Mr. Coconut.
Please make a mock VTR.
I didn't write it.
Impossible, impossible, impossible.
Thank you.
And now, let the Seishun Zombies music video begin!
Hey!
Oh, oh, oh, here it comes.
Too emo at the end, I hear.
Yes, it is.
Wow.
What did you think, everyone?
Even if you just saw it.
I love it.
It's a great music video.
Hey, it was a lot of fun.
Did you want to play a zombie? Because I wanted to play a zombie.
But you know what, we're not there yet.
I mean, we've done the whole kyung shi thing, but...
I've never really worn that kind of makeup.
I've been told by my sisters that I'm a "kyong shi".
Yes, they did.
They did, but Yuno and the others won.
When we talked about who to choose...
They all agreed on Miree.
I've never seen her before.
I think they did in the past.
You know...
You know, you're so good with the zombie moves.
That's true.
She could draw so well.
That was great.
It was fun.
And the last scene...
In the very last scene, you expanded a lot of places with Yuno and the others.
That's right.
The staff tried to inflate all of them.
It's all in the bag.
How many?
About 10.
They were all inflated.
That's what I'm talking about.
You did it.
I started playing with it halfway through, though, before I tied it up.
That's great.
They were taking a lot of videos of us blowing up the balloons.
That's true.
Yunopiappia!
Yunopi did a great job, didn't she?
Oh, no...
Did you get better?
I couldn't get it to expand at all in the beginning.
But by the end, you looked like a pro.
You're a pro at inflating.
I got the hang of it.
It was fun.
We had fun.
Can we watch the making of? Is there a making of?
I think so. It was making the rounds.
Well, you'll have to wait and see.
Enjoy.
What do you think?
Please send me more feedback.
I'm sending them.
I'm sending you more.
More? More, please.
More, please.
The thumbnails are cute.
The thumbnails are so good!
You know, for a second there, Hinata-chan...You know, Hinata, for a moment...
I wondered where she was, but she's the biggest one.
Oh, my God.
The part with the glasses.
It's a big picture.
And then there's Cocona's.
I don't know if I should say this, but...
I don't know if I should say this, but those pants were amazing.
Oh, I see.
The pants of the outfit, like a casual outfit.
The pants...
There was an opening.
He said, "You're in the hashtag.
I laughed a little.
It's empty.
And the outfits... everyone's outfits...
I mean, it was very much me, or rather, the members.
It was so cute!
I thought it was really cute.
I thought they were so cute.
It was so cute!
The short-sleeved type and the short pants type
And the short pants type pajamas.
Not that one.
But pajamas like that.
I see.
They were so cute!
So...
That's all.
That's all for now.
Thank you so much!
I'm looking forward to the day of the live performance!
Okay, and next up...
Today we're going to do this project.
Find the funniest and huffiest liars!
Yay!
Now the three of you
I'm going to ask you a question.
Out of the three of you, two of you will tell the truth
One of them is lying, so
Users can vote in a poll
Find out who is lying by voting.
Find out who's lying.
Sounds like a werewolf.
Yes, it is.
I'm a good liar.
I mean, you're a liar.
Who's a good liar?
I'm a good liar
I thought it was Junopi.
Yuno lies.
Yuno...
Nonaka was studying for something.
And he was explaining everything to Cocona.
And I said, "Yuno, whose kid is this?
I said, "Whose kid?" and he said, "Huh?
And she was like, "What?
It's like a lie that's true.
That's right.
Now that they think it's true.
So let's do the lie.
Let's lie.
Who's going to lie?
All of you.
You can guess.
Yes, sir.
I'll announce the questions for the lie.
Dinner tonight.
Last night's dinner.
I can't remember.
Yesterday's dinner
What day was yesterday?
Monday
What did you do on Monday?
On Monday...
We each had our own thing.
Wait, wait, wait.
I know what I'm doing.
I remember.
Oh, God.
Wait, wait, wait.
How's it going?
Uh...
What do you think?
Did everyone get it?
Are we going to give these out one at a time?
Yes, that's right. Who would like to go first?
The first person to write?
Okay, I'll start with Nonaka.
Then I'll ask for one minute to 30 seconds to one minute of conversation.
Let's talk.
All of you.
Hey.
I can't do it alone.I can't do it alone.
Hey, hey.
All of us.
Let's do it together.
Okay. I made curry and rice for dinner last night.
My mom suddenly said she wanted to eat curry, so she went out and bought curry ingredients and made tomato-based curry rice.
It was really delicious.
It's good.
Shall we go now?
Okay, let's go.
What?
Already?
Are you sure? Can't we just go a little bit longer?
Wait.
Everyone's getting confused. They're saying, "Go there." Are you okay with that?
What's the filling for the curry and rice?
I don't know, not the usual potatoes and carrots, but spinach?
You put spinach in it.
Like spinach. There were carrots in it, but if it was spinach, pork, carrots, and smaller ingredients, it didn't look like a lot of spinach.
Looks delicious.
It was delicious.
Then, let me eat it for the throat winner.
Okay.
Next.
Here. Onigiri.
Onigiri?
Really?
No, that was the last one.
You know, I had onigiri yesterday. I had a fried rice ball from a convenience store.
Fried rice balls.
It was delicious.
That's all?
Yes, that's all.
Really?
Really.
That's all? Really?
What? This sounds so fake.
Are you full?
What? Are you crazy? Are you eating a snack?
It's not candy.
Sweets.
I knew it.
It sounds so fake, but it's true.
It's true. What do you think?
Onigiri.
Yes, I did.
I ate onigiri.
What about you, Ms. Kokana?
Yes, I did. Jansan. Cheese takkarbi.
It looks like she's eating something.
That's right. You like Korean food, right?
Yes, I do.
Yesterday, my mom and I were wondering what we should eat, and we decided to go with Korean spicy food,
Cheese and takkarbi. We decided to have cheese and takkarbi.
I had the cheese takkarbi.
Was it spicy?
Yes, it was. A little spicy. I can eat spicy or not, so I made it very spicy. I put a lot of gochujang in it.
It was really good.
It's the best. Everyone.
Is this at home? I asked.
At home.
We did it at home on a hot plate. We did it together.
That's nice. Looks delicious.
It was delicious.
We all look suspicious, don't we? This.
This is all suspicious.
First of all, let's review.
I made curry and rice.
Rice balls.
Cheese takkarbi for me.
Number tags.
Vote by number to see who lies.
I wonder.
If the member who lied is in first place, Yuzura wins, and if the member who lied is in second or third place, Ebichu wins.
What will happen?
Let's start.
They suspect me a lot.
This is very difficult.
It's in Ibaraki.
You can eat cheese takkarbi anywhere.
Even here, it's often called cheese takkarbi.
I eat Korean food.
What did you often eat when you were Kami-San?
You ate a lot, didn't you?
Kimchi, for example.
That's right.
I had a lot of kimchi in my yakiniku.
What do you think?
I heard that he is doing surprisingly well.
That's not true.
He's not here.
It's about time.
Five, four, three, two, one, stop.
Okay, the voting is over.
It's over.
Who lied?
Yes, it was me. I've been caught.
I think I did pretty well.
I think I did pretty well, but I don't know how everyone knew I was at home.
I was lost and confused with everyone else, so that was a lie.
He said he was going to eat at home, but he said he was going to eat at home because he was going to eat at home.He said he was going to go out to eat because he was doing it at home, and his mom and I were going out to eat on a cheese day.
How could you ask me that? I'm so stupid.
What did you really eat?
I ate ramen, not Nakamoto's.
But ramen's the same, right?
I want to eat kalbi at home now. So the user wins.
It's difficult, isn't it?
Oh, you're a liar!
Stajawa, you're up.
Please do. What's more, onigiri? Yes, they were. They were delicious. The onigiri was too weird.
They were delicious. Yes, it was. A nickname I've been called. Is this one?
One. Yes. That's weird.
What do they call you?
Okay, I got it. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Heh.
Huh?
Hmm.
How's it going? Gentlemen.
I can see this.
I'm lost.
I can't remember.
I don't know.
I don't want to have a disreputable name, but that's all I have. In the first place.
Ha-ha-ha.
What do you think?
Wow, this is so difficult. I wonder.
This is really well done, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Yes. Please write it down.
Okay.
Yes.
How's it going? Did you put coconut oil on it?
I did!
I'm fine too.
Okay, are you okay?
Okay, what's next?
You're going to make an announcement?
Yes, I am.
Yes, I'm Jean! I'm Kotetsu!
Kotetsu!
What? Why?
Do you know who Kotetsu is?
Maybe not.
There's something called kote-chan that you eat with rice.
What's that? What's in it?
I don't know, it's kind of tasty.
Is it an accompaniment?
An accompaniment.
Coconut is what my mom calls me, sometimes.
She calls me that when I beg her,
Kotetsu! Wash the bathtub! And so on.
It's pretty much like this.
I've never been called "kokonar.
My mom calls me Kotetsu and Kote-chan, or Kokotan.
Yes, and Shino-san?
Yes, fried chicken.
What?
Tell me when I was in elementary school.
Wait, wait!
Is that true?
Really?
Really.
When we were in elementary school, I told you that you tanned very easily, didn't I?
Oh, that's right.
I had black, black feet and all.
In elementary school?
Birds have very thin legs.
That's why they were black.
Yes, they are very thin at home.
That's why they were even thinner.
I was surprised a little when Kamo-chan called me "Chun-chan.
So I was a little surprised when Kamo-chan called me "Chunchan.
I was in elementary school.
That's why.
I see.
I guess that's true.
I thought you said it's not "zangi" anymore.
Zangi is different.
Zangyi.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes.
Then I'll go next.
I, yes.
Nompi.
I don't know why, but when I was in elementary school,
I don't know why, but there were so many names for me,
Some kids called me NONKA-chan, which is pretty normal,
But there was a girl who called me "Nompi,
There are a lot of "NONKA-chan" and "NONPI-chan",
There are a lot of "NONKA-chan",
That's right. There are a lot of NON-chan.
I thought it's unusual to see NON-chan with a "T".
That's true.
I was surprised.
Nonpy.
That's right.
Nonpy is cute.
He's cute.Cute.
Now what do you think?
Then who.
Yes.
Shall we review?
I'll review.
First of all, I'm Kotetsu.
Yes, I am.
Yuno is Karaage.
Yes. I'm Nompi.
Nompi.
Then let's start the voting.
Let's start.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Start.
But it looks like everyone is here.
The reason is great.
Because it's true.
I'm convinced.
What do you think?
It's definitely coming.
I'm sure he's here. Did you arrange Yu's purity?
I don't know.
The presence of fried bean curd is amazing.
That's right.
Two out of three people eat it.
What do you think?
I'm about to close it.
Four, three, two, one.
The end.
Okay. What will happen now?
The real result.
Here you go.
Second place is first place, third place is first place.
Third place is second?
First place is second.
Second place is third.
Third place is first.
So, yes, for now.
I lied.
Yes.
You're early, Gen.
You're fast.
My real nickname is burdock.
Oh, that's right.
I was called burdock because my legs were really black and thin.
I think it was Yuno's cousin who called me Karage.
He really existed.
It's difficult here, too.
I keep thinking about it, but it's difficult.
It's difficult. I don't think about it.
It's amazing.
Shizan-san is amazing.
It was burdock root, wasn't it?
Mr. Burdock.
Also, he called me Yunori. My little brother called me Yunori.
Yunori?
Because I like Yunori.
No, I probably just called him Yunori without thinking about it.
Heh.
But it's perfect. I like yunori.
That's true.
Indeed.
So, Yuzasan has won both questions.
It's not good. It's a little bit.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Let's go for it.
No, no, no, it's one to one, one to one.
Why one-on-one?
Because I was number two.
Because I was 7 earlier.
I see.
I thought you were lying.
Yes, yes, yes.
One to one.
One-one-one.
Okay, next.
Rust.
Let's go to Rust.
Okay. Okay, I'll start.
My future dream as a child.
Dreams of the future.
I see.
I remember this very well.
What's that? What is it? Wait a minute. Let's work a little harder. Let's just hang on a second.
What... what... what was... what... what was that?
Well, it's a great picture.
Oh, I remember now.
What was it?
Good morning.
Okay, I'm going to go to the masked rider show.
Yes, you know, my brother was watching Kamen Rider all the time, so I was watching it beside him, and I like Kamen Rider very much.
I see... there is no such thing... a movie
That picture is the white masked rider... the welfare guy... Ultraman...
No, it's Ultraman
Kamen Rider is cute. It's not Ultraman.Kamen Rider's cute, but I'm not Ultraman
I'm going to go to the cake shop.
My friend and I were thinking we'd work together in the future.
I liked them, so we decided to work together in a cake shop.
I'm a walking model for ramen noodles.
I wanted to be one of those cool walking models on TV... and I was practicing my dance moves.
I have a lot of memories of that.
I'm going to start the voting, so please enter the number of this ballot
I saw you say "FOURZE" in the comments earlier and I thought, "Ah, FOURZE!
I've been watching it since I was about that age.
It looks difficult...
Mr. Sakuragi, you have a character. What's that? He's a Yankee, so I'll tell you.
Okay, let's end the voting. Five, four, three, two, one.
Voting's over. Here are the results.
Yes, please!
How's it going?
So 2 is number 2 and 13 is number 1.
May I sing now? Okay. Okay.
Then someone noticed that I'm kind of an idol.
He's like, "What's up?
You're the one who said that.
That's right.
Open.
Oh, no.
Why can't I smile?
Okay.
Who is your idol?
Adéle.
Okay, solo.
Solo.
One of them.
I mean, you don't get better at lying.
I know. Let's go for it.
Yes, sir. And so.
The 46th edition of the Shrimp in the Shrimp Showroom is now open.
Oh, I don't have to tell you here.
I was lied to.
Yay!
Well, I'll go next time.
This is the 46th episode of the showroom of the funniest and most hilarious of the shrimpers and it's quickly coming to an end!
Okay.
Then I'll make an announcement.
Yes, please. Please do.
First of all, the major debut of Ebi Junior High School in Japan, the 2nd september tour after school, and the Taiwan item for it has been announced today.
And the Taiwan item was announced today.
Yes, that's right. Yes. First of all, Zep Nagoya
July 21 is the date of the event.
Yes.
July 22 is Mr. Yoshidan
Yes. And Zep Haneda
July 25th is Tetsu Okazaki-san
Yup.
July 26th will be Angelem!
There are many more who have yet to be announced, so please look forward to them!
Please look forward to it!
And also...
Is this your first time in Taiwan?
That's right.
It's the first time we want to do it by ourselves, so we're looking forward to it.
Yes. And
Kato and Aya's birthday party will be starting soon!
Yes, sir.
Kato's solo birthday live 4&7 will be held on June 13th
at KT Jep Yokohama
Yes, sir!
And Aya-chan's birthday solo show "Sing, Dance and Sing Show Yasuyasu" will be held on June 14 at KT Jep Yokohama and on June 27 at Namba Hatch!
I'm looking forward to it!
And there is one more thing...
Yes!
Ebichu Summer Family Production
Translated into "Famien 2022", it's going to be held!
Yay!
The place is Yamanakako Koryu Plaza
at Koryu Plaza Kirarashi Ata Hibiki
Yay!
It will be held on August 6th and 7th.
This year, we're going to have our voice out...
Yes, this is a little bit...
There is an area where you can speak out.
I'll be there.
Please look forward to it.
I hope you're looking forward to it.
There's also a relaxation area.
Yes, we do.
Well, then, enjoy the show.
I'll announce the final ranking.
Okay.
Thank you very much, Ega.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Maru Kawaba.
Thank you very much
Thank you, Mr. Monta, 3rd place
Thank you very much!
Thank you, Kohei Hokkaido (2nd place)
Thank you, Tamamin (1st place)
Thank you very much.
Yes, ma'am.
Then, it's a showroom, isn't it?Then it's a showroom.
It was, wasn't it?
Yes, sir.
Let's make an announcement.
So...
You were the MC.
Don't tell me.
The deadline for auditioning new members is...
That's right.
Yes, sir.
It's until June 10th.
We're waiting for your applications.
If you have any doubts, please do not hesitate to apply.
If you are not sure, please apply now!
Please apply now while you still can!
Please apply now!
We're looking forward to hearing from you!
Please, please, please, please.
Now then...
The 46th showroom of Shrimps in the middle of the shrimp
This is the end of the 46th showroom.
Yes, sir.
And an important announcement.
The next broadcast will be on Monday, July 11th at 8:00 p.m.
Yes, sir.
This broadcast is...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
This distribution will take place after this.
We don't have time for this.
There's no time, so...
You know what?
I'll see you next time.
July 11th.
Yes.
It's going to be Monday at 8:00 p.m.
Reflection
Reflections one by one
Impressions
Well then, Yukonasan
From me
Yes, you are right.
I was very worried about YUNON's MC, but
But I really enjoyed it.
I thought that YUNON would like to do it again with the three of us.
It was a lot of fun.
I'll go now.
Yes, I'm going.
I'll go to YUNON.
Let's see, YUNON...
What is it again?
Hohoho hoho
It's not a ho ho ho...
A little more
I'll do music videos again.
It's not a music video
There may be a time for MC, so...
I'll do my best
I'll do my best.
Yes, I will.
And Yuko.
Well, I think I was able to speak better than last time.
Yes, you did.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm glad.
Well, I'll try to do better next time I'm MC.
Yes, sir.
That's all for now.
Bye bye.
Thank you very much.